[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What interesting characteristic do all amphibians called caecilians share?", "correct_answer": "They have no legs.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are hermaphrodites.", "They have four eyes.", "They have external ears."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All cell proteins are embedded in the cell membrane.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor took the award for Best Actor in a Leading Role at the 72nd Academy Awards 2000?", "correct_answer": "Kevin Spacey", "incorrect_answers": ["Denzel Washington", "Russell Crowe", "Sean Penn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the antagonist in Steven Spielbergs 1981 movie Raiders of the Lost Ark?", "correct_answer": "The Nazis", "incorrect_answers": ["The Russian Secret Service", "All of these", "The French Secret Service"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wombats are endemic to this geographical area.", "correct_answer": "Australia and Tasmania", "incorrect_answers": ["South America", "Madagascar", "Indonesia and the Philippines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors voices Diego, the saber-tooth tiger from Ice Age 3?", "correct_answer": "Denis Leary", "incorrect_answers": ["Rowan Atkinson", "Mike Myers", "Justin Timberlake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Turtles can breathe in water.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This President, often called by his opponents His Accidency,  was the first politician to assume the office of US President following the death of his predecessor.", "correct_answer": "John Tyler", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Johnson", "Richard Nixon", "James Buchanan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the seat of colonial government in Maryland until 1708?", "correct_answer": "St. Mary\u2019s City", "incorrect_answers": ["Annapolis", "Port Tobacco", "Baltimore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these nicknames refers to the U.S. state of Idaho?", "correct_answer": "Gem State", "incorrect_answers": ["Emerald State", "Pearl State", "Golden State"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is James Browns honorific nickname?", "correct_answer": "Godfather of Soul", "incorrect_answers": ["King of Jazz", "King of the Blues", "Chairman of the Board"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Jack and Rose at the end of the 1997 movie Titanic, which set a record for the highest-grossing movie in history?", "correct_answer": "Jack dies and Rose moves on with her life", "incorrect_answers": ["They die in the shipwreck.", "They survive and get married.", "Rose dies and Jack kills himself."]}]